<Publish>
  <ModId Value="92671" />
  <DisplayName Value="StarQ's Workflow Kit" />
  <ShortDescription Value="The ULTIMATE mod to satisfy all your need. JK!" />
  <LongDescription># StarQ Workflow Kit
This mod is primarily to be used by prefab asset creators.

This mod modify prefabs in an irreversible way. So, make sure to Backup your local prefabs in case anything goes wrong.

## Features
* Prefab Saver: Resave prefab to remove the pesky "m_LargeIcon" and/or "m_FireHazard" issue from any prefab files, create CID if missing or convert prefabs from Text format to Binary format and vice versa.
* Prefab Packager: Create COK packages from prefabs.
* Prefab Modifier: Bulk prefab modification to add UI Icons, PlaceableObject, UIGroup, EditorAssetCategoryOverride, AssetPack; remove ObsoleteIdentifiers, SpawnableObject, AssetPack.
* Locale Maker: Create vanilla localization files from JSON (I18N) locale.
* Optional 'EditorAssetCategoryOverride' for all assets based on its prefab type.
* That's all... Oh, and the PDX upload script.

## PDXM CS2 Uploader
Make sure the Modding Toolchain is completely installed. .NET6.0 (which is part of the Modding Toolchain .NET SDK) is required for the Uploader to open up.
Copy 'PDXM_CS2_Uploader_vX.X.X.exe' to an empty folder outside any CS2 folders. This will be your project folder, just for one mod. Launch the application once to set up folder structure following the on-screen instructions.
VT Scan: https://www.virustotal.com/gui/file/278f418a39e7939fe98c2c335647c28513be2e8bd94837bdd5c36870da55641d

## DISCLAIMER
This mod modifies experimental custom contents in an irreversible way.
The mod author is not responsible for any change in content resulting from its use.
The mod author is not responsible for any content uploaded using the PDXM CS2 Uploader.
	</LongDescription>
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <Tag Value="Code Mod" />
  <ModVersion Value="2.0.2" />
  <GameVersion Value="1.3.3f1" />
  <ChangeLog>
- Uploader 2.0.2: Reduce prompts
- Uploader 2.0.2: Fix update check bug
- Uploader 2.0.2: Changed text colors
- Uploader 2.0.2: Added translation support
	</ChangeLog>
  <ExternalLink Type="buymeacoffee" Url="https://buymeacoffee.com/starq" />
  <ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/U2PSjUzUuF" />
</Publish>
